Previously on...
[绝望主妇]前情提要...
i'm going to be a stay-at-home dad. Huh?
我要做一个家庭妇男
Some reversed roles... i've been think in' about you.
- 我一直在想你
So you came to ask me out?
那么你要约我出去吗?
Some were welcomed in... 'cause i'll say yes.
[有些人受到款待...] 我答应了
I've moved on. You should do the same.
我决定继续生活下去了 你应该学学我
Some were shn the door...
[有些人被拒之门外...]
will you marry me?
你愿意嫁给我吗?
And some... huh?
[还有些人...]
Never got the chance... aah!
[从没有得到机会...]
To find out what they really wanted.
[去发现他们真正想要的东西]
Betty applewhite was a gifted woman.
[Betty applewhite是个有才华的女人]
Everyone had always said so ever since she was a child.
[自从她小的时候起  所有人就都这么说]
Her first piano teacher praised her dexterity.
[她的第一个钢琴老师赞扬她手指灵巧]
Her first college professor
[她的大学教授]
applauded her sense of rhythm...
[为她对节奏的判断力大加赞誉...]
Her first symphony conductor hailed her dramatic flair...
[她的第一个交响乐指挥向她 生动的演绎才华致敬...]
But betty was no longer a concert pianist.
[但是betty不再是一位音乐会钢琴演奏家了]
She was now just a woman with a secret,
[她现在只是一位身怀秘密的女人]
one she was determined to keep by any means necessary.
[一个她决定无论如何都要保守的秘密]
that someby broke into gabrielle's house.
有人会闯入gabrielle的房子 我一点也不惊奇
Wisteria lane is an easy target.
Wisteria Lane是一个容易攻击的目标
It's not like the police patrol around here.
没有巡警会巡查这里
We still have the neighborhood watch.
我们一直有邻里监督组织的
Oh,the neighborhood watch is a joke.
哦 邻里监督组织简直就是搞笑
When was the last time any of you went on patrol,huh?
你上一次出来巡逻时什么时候,嗯哈?
Now i put security lights on my house.
我现在给我的房子安装了安全灯
I say it's time that we hire professional security.
依我说 是该雇佣专业保安的时候了
Well,that sounds expensive.
哇噢 那听起来很贵阿
Could you really put a price on your kids' safety?
你不愿意为你孩子的安全花些钱吗?
Well,you probably could. Look,mcclusky,i am as worried
听着 Mcclusky夫人 我和附近的邻里的 所有人一样的担忧
as everybody else in this neighborhood,but i just...
我和附近的邻里的 所有人一样的担忧, 但我只是...
(hushed voice) We've got to stop this.
我们应该制止他们这样
(hushed voice) and say what, we're against security?
- 那怎么讲  我们要反对安全保护吗? .
But if they find caleb first... hush,matthew. I'm trying to think.
- 安静 matthew 我正在想呢
I'm not talking about a bunch of vigilantes,
- 我不想谈论那些义务的警员
i'm taing about trained men who know when to shoot.
我们需要的是受过专业训练的会开枪的人
(tom) do we really need professional security?
我们真的需要专业的保安吗?
(mrs. Mcclusky) Are you all gonna wait
你们所有人还要等待着 直到又有人受到袭击吗?
I think it's time to take a vote on armed security.
我认为现在应该投票决定
(all talking at once) (man) let's vote now.
让我们现在投票吧
I've had enough. All those in favor...
我已经受够了 你们支持...
Oh,sorry. Things were just getting so dramatic.
哦 抱歉 刚才我看事态有点激化了
Wow,you're really good.
哇奥 你弹得真棒
We were taking a vote here.
- 我们要投票
She was a concert pianist.
她是音乐会钢琴演奏家
Well,i dabbled a bit.
嗯  也就学了几下
Yes,betty applewhite was a gifted woman...
是啊 betty applewhite是一位有才华的女性...
and the greatest of all her gifts...
她最棒的才华就是...
Some women sit alone in the dark for hours.
[有些女人会孤单的呆在黑暗中数小时]
They refuse to go out in the light of day,
[他们拒绝白天外出]
afraid to face the possibility that life will go on.
[不敢想像继续生活下去是什么样子]
They hold onto reminders of their unborn child
[他们留恋着能让他们想起还未出生的孩子的东西]
and dream of what might have been.
[并且幻想一切可能发生的事情]
Yes,this is how some women react
[是的 这就是一些女人当他们面对 流产时所表现的反应]
Gabrielle solis was not one of those women.
[Gabrielle solis则不属于这类女人]
Hi,guys.
嗨 姑娘们
Hi,honey. Hi.
嗨 亲爱的 嗨 你怎么样?
I'm... i'm sorry i haven't had time to return calls.
我... 很抱歉我没有时间回复它们
We all cleared our schedules.
我们都取消了我们的预约
We thought maybe you could use some company.
我们想也许你需要人陪陪
So we're going to go to my house.
所以 我们准备去我那里
I made banana bread, and we'll put on a fresh pot,
我做了香蕉面包 我们一起打打牌
and just talk about anything.
聊聊天
That sounds so nice.
听起来不错啊 只是我今天的安排很紧
It's just i'm booked solid today.
只是我今天的安排很紧
My head's gonna explode.
我的头快要炸了
Can i take a rain check?
改日吧？
Sure.
当然可以
Thanks.
谢谢
Thanks for understanding.
感谢你们的理解
Okay,well,uh, i will call you tonight
好的 嗯 我今晚会给你打电话 我们本周再选个时间
and we'll figure out a time later in the week. Well,i'll tell you what,
好的 嗯 我今晚会给你打电话 我们本周再选个时间 好啊 要不这么吧
since it's my schedule that seems to be the problem,
既然是我预约有问题
why don't i just figure out a time and call you?
何不我选好时间 再打电话通知你呢?
Okay.
好的
I st... i have so many errands to run
我... 我有很多事情要处理 这么多的东西要去退换
and a llion things to return.
Oh,honey,there's no reason why you and carlos can't try again.
哦 亲爱的 你和carlos没有理由不再试一下
You'd be an amazing mother.
你会是一个好妈妈的
You should hold onto that stuff for a while.
东西还是别急着退回去
Yeah,you know,i would,
是 你们要知道 我会的
but the store has this strict 30-day return policy.
但是 商店有30天的退换期政策
Carlos,what happened?
Carlos 发生了什么?
I've had a rough couple days. (sniffles)
这几天过得不好
After you told me about the...
就在你告诉我...
(sighs) the baby...
孩子没了后...
i kind of lost it.
我有些无所适从
Carlos,your hands.
Carlos 你的手 我撕开了床垫
I ripped my mattress open.
我撕开了床垫
Jeez,how are you feeling today?
天呀 你感觉如何?
They're injecting me with this tranquilizer thing.
为了让我冷静下来 他们给我注射了镇静剂
I think it's doing the trick.
我想这样我可以好些
(sighs) we never even talked about names.
我们还从没有商量过孩子的名字
I had my top five all picked out.
我已经挑选了五个候选的名字
You want to hear 'em?
- 你要听听吗?
No,i'm good.
不 我很好
But you never thought about names?
你从没有想过孩子的名字?
Oh,well,it was a little soon for that,don't you think?
噢 嗯 想名字是不是太早了点 你觉得呢?
I mean,how can you name something the size of a walnut?
我的意思是 孩子现在才那么小 你就取名字啊？
Is this new?
这是新买的?
Do you like it? I picked it up on the way here.
你喜欢吗? 我在来这儿的路上买的
You just lost a baby.
你刚刚没了孩子
We all grieve differently.
人人都有自己悲伤的方式 你看起来没什么事啊
You seem to be takin' it pretty well.
你看起来没什么事啊
I go shopping,you rip toilets out of the wall...
我去购物 你砸座便器
Oh,please. What do you think?
哦 拜托 你在想什么?
Honestly? I don't know.
说实话 我不知道
Of course,i'm sad. It's a sad situation.
说实话 我不知道 当然 我伤心啦 这是个伤心事
Now let go of me.
放开我
Oh,man.
- 哦 天啊
Honey,are you okay?
亲爱的 你还好吧?
I think my tranquilizer's wearing off.
我想我的镇静剂药效减退了
Well,let's get you another round.
那得给你再来一针呀
Hey,mike.
嗨 mike
So my mom's wedding's in a couple days,
过几天是我妈妈的婚礼
and i know you sent back that little card
我知道你送回了那个小卡片
saying you were coming and that you preferred beef,
说你会来 还喜欢牛肉
which,actually, i changed to fish for you
不过我换成鱼了 因为我尝过牛肉了
'cause i tasted the beef.
Anyways,i know that was before we,you know.
不管怎样 我知道那是在我们分手之前的事了
Send your mom my apologies,
替我对你妈妈说声对不起
but i won't be attending. Oh.
但是 我不会参加的
I hope that's not just because of us not being us anymore.
我希望那不是因为我们分手的原因
I mean,we could be together at a wedding,
我的意思是 我们可以一起出席婚礼宴会啊
and it wouldn't have to be weird.
那样并不会显得很不自然
It'd be weird.
那样会很不自然的
Of course. Yeah,i see that.
当然 是的 我明白了
So what have you been doing lately?
那么你近来有什么安排?
Oh,just the usual.
哦 和往常一样
Well,i've been writing a book.
那好 我最近在写一本书
It's sort of autobiographical.
有几分自传体的感觉
It's really been forcing me to reexamine
写书让我去自省
some of the different things that have made me me,
我之所以如今这样的经历
like the fact that my mother had me so young,
比如我妈妈年轻的时候就有了我
and i never knew my dad. Big stuff like that.
我从不知道我父亲是谁 诸如此类的事情
I told you about my dad,right?
我和你说过我父亲 对吗? 他... 他是一个商船队的船员
He... he was a merchant marine,
他... 他是一个商船队的船员
and his platoon was killed in the battle of hanoi?
他们在河内战役的时候被杀了?
That's strange.
- 那很奇怪啊
Why?
为什么?
Well, hanoi wasn't enemy territory.
嗯 河内不是敌方的区域 那里也没有战役发生
There wasn't a battle there. Are you sure?
你确信吗?那是我妈妈说的
That's what my mom said. I'm pretty sure,yeah.
你确信吗?那是我妈妈说的 我非常明确
The merchant marines don't fight.
商船队不参战的
They deliv supplies on ships.
他们只是负责船上的补给
Oh. Well,clearly i have more research to do.
哦 看来我还得好好研究研究
So what do you think?
那么你有什么想法?
My life story... would you rush out and buy a copy?
我的生活经历 你会迫不及待的买一本吗?
Susan...
- Susan...
yeah?
什么?
You really need to step back.
你应该退后一点
Porter,preston, what have i told you
Porter,preston,我是怎么和你们说的? 关于天黑后在外面玩?
about playing outside after dark? It's not dark.
Porter,preston,我是怎么和你们说的? 关于天黑后在外面玩? 不黑
Does your dad know you're out here? Don't worry, i've been watching 'em.
不黑 爸爸知道你们在外面吗? 不用担心,我看着他们呢
They keep setting off my motion sensors.
他们不停的触动我的感应器
I ought to send you half my electric bill.
我要给你寄一半的电费单
You do that. Okay,guys,come on over here.
好的 孩子们,过来
On the sidewalk.
到人行道上来
Stay there. Not on the street. Thank you.
不要走到路上，谢谢
Hey.
嘿，宝贝
Hi,babe. (turns off vacuum)
我回来了
Could you come here a sec?
能过来会吗?
Sure. What's up?
可以，怎么了?
Block me,come on!
拦住我,来啊!
Damn,they must have snuck out again.
该死，他们又溜出来了
Again? How often does this happen?
又出来了?经常发生吗？
Boys,get in here now!
孩子们，快进来
Honey,you know how slippery they are.
宝贝，你知道他们多机灵
It's like trying to herd cats.
就像是赶猫一样
Tom,it's 9:00 at night.
Tom,已经晚上9点了
Guys,upstairs now. Let's go.
孩子们，上楼，快
Into pj's,into bed. Honey,they're fine.
上床去 亲爱的，他们没事
You just... you worry too much.
你太担心了
And for good reason.
是有原因的
Someone could have driven off with them,
他们可能被拐走
and you wouldn't have even noticed.
而你根本就不会发现
They were in the front yard. God,when i was their age,
他们就在门口 当我像他们那个年纪的时候
i used to hop on my bike, disappear for hours.
我曾经骑车好几个小时不回家
My mom never batted an eye.
我妈妈根本不管我
Yeah,well, that was a different time.
是啊，时代不同啊
You have to be more vigilant.
你必须要警惕
There was a break-in on this street.
这条街上发生过闯入事件
I was at the neighborhood watch meeting,remember?
邻里联防会我也出席了，记得吗？
I'm sorry. I've been doing this for seven years.
我照顾他们已经7年了
Trust me. You have to have eyes in the back of your head.
相信我，你要多看着他们 多个心眼
The two in front work just fine,thanks. Really?
那两个在门口玩的很好
Mm-hmm. Where's penny?
是吗? penny在哪?
See? Right where i left her.
看到了?就在这 我把她放在这的
How did this get in the paper
这个怎么会在报纸上?
l-i was going to call you.
这个怎么会在报纸上? 我打算告诉你的
We discussed this. We agreed to go slowly.
我们讨论过这个 我们要从长计议
L-i was going to call and cancelfter our talk,
我们谈过后,我就想取消这个
but things just got so hectic, l-i forgot.
但事情很多，我就忘了
Rex has only been dead for seven weeks.
Rex过世才7个星期
So?
所以?
So i don't want every woman in this town
所以我不想这个镇上每个女人都在我背后说闲话
talking about me behind my back.
I'm sorry, but isn't the damage done?
我很抱歉 没造成什么损害吧？
Well,fortunately,people only read the announcements
幸运的是 只有头版什么都没有时
when there's nothing in the front page,
人们才会去看公告
some catastrophic flood in sri lanka. Oh,so we lucked out.
今天的头条是关于斯里兰卡的水灾 哦 这么说我们运气好极了 是的 我们确实是
Yes,we did.
是的 我们确实是
i need you to discuss it with me first.
我需要你先和我商量一下
I'm the bride,after all. It's only...
毕竟 我是新娘 那样才...
appropriate.
合适 好吧
Okay.
好吧
I will need you to wear that ring,though.
尽管如此我还是需要你戴上戒指
You're not wearing it. Where is it?
你没戴 戒指在哪?
It's in my purse.
-在我的手袋里
Oh,good.
哦 太棒了
Please put it on.
请你戴上
But if people see it...
但如果有人看到的话...
they'll assume that you're wearing your wedding ring.
他们都会认为你是带着你的结婚戒指 哦 可能 但为什么要冒这个险呢?
Oh. Maybe,but why risk it?
哦 可能 但为什么要冒这个险呢?
Because a ring tells would-be suitors a woman is spoken for.
因为戒指代表一个女人已经有了求婚者
A naked hand invites unwanted attention.
而光秃秃的手指会带来不必要的关注
Here. Let me.
过来 让我来
Uh,will that be all, mrs. Van de kamp?
呃 就这些了吗 Van de Camp夫人?
Uh,yes,i think so, mr. Williams.
呃 是的 我想是的 Williams先生
Oh,my god!
哦 我的上帝啊!
What do you want?!
你想干什么?!
Hey,hey,it's cool!
你想干什么?! 嘿 嘿 没关系的!
No,it's not cool! Who the hell are you?!
不 有关系! 你究竟是谁?!
Carlos sent me!
- Carlos让我来的!
I'm gonna call the police!
我可要报警了!
Name's hector. I met carlos inside.
我叫Hector 我在里面认识的Carlos
Inside what?
什么里面?
You mean... you mean,in prison?
你是说...你是说 牢里面?
He told me what happened, asked me to come by
他告诉了我之前发生的事 他要我过来保护你
Can I come in?
- 我能进来吗?
No! No,you can't come in!
不! 不 不准进来
I brought a cooler. I'll camp out here. No! Unh-unh!
我带了喝的 我可以在外面露宿
I can take care of myself,okay?
不! 我能照顾自己 好吗?
Okay.
好的
Okay?
好的?
Yeah,l-i get it. You need your space.
是啊 我懂 你需要空间
Yes. Yes,i do. I need my space. Thank you.
是 我需要 我需要空间 谢谢
Come here. I want to show you something. Okay.
过来 我想让你看点东西
Come here.
- 过来
Hi,guys.
嗨 伙计们
I thought about what you said.
我考虑过你说的了
Don't want you to worry.
我不想让你担心
So i had a little talk with the boys.
所以我和儿子们谈了谈
if a stranger asks us to take a ride in their car?
如果有陌生人让我们上他车 我们怎么办?
We run away and call 9-1-1.
- 我们跑开然后打911
Good man.
好样的
Right,but what if that stranger says,
对的 但如果那个陌生人说
"hey,i know your mommy and daddy"?
“嘿 我认识你的爸爸妈妈呢？”
What,preston?
- 就怎样 Preston?
Still run away.
还是跑开
Yes. Okay...
对了 好吧...
can i ask a question?
- 我能问个问题吗?
Yeah,by all means.
可以 什么都行
What if the stranger is nice and not scary?
如果那个陌生人很友善还一点都不可怕呢?
Yes?
什么?
Run away and call 9-1-1.
还是跑开然后打911
So what if the stranger says
那如果那个陌生人说
for pizza and elephant rides?
他们要带你去马戏团吃披萨、骑大象呢?
Don't look at your dad.
别看你爸爸
Eyes on me. What are you gonna do?
看着我 你会怎么做?
What are you gonna do?
你会怎么做?
We...
我们...
run away?
跑开？
Yes! Snap.
对了! 好样的
Okay,to the kitchen.
好吧 去厨房
We are havin' ice cream tonight.
我们今晚吃冰激凌
Your smiling like that actually meant something.
你笑成那样很能说明问题了
Lynette,come on. We worked on this all afternoon. They get it.
Lynette 拜托 我们一个下午都在说这个 他们知道了
Give me a break. You know our kids. I love them dearly,
你拉倒吧 你了解我们的孩子 我非常爱他们
but that goes in one ear and out the other.
但他们总是左朵进 右朵出的
Tom,you're not off the hook here.
我要去吃点冰激凌了 Tom 你还没完事呢
Lynette,i can keep my children alive.
Lynette 我有能力让我的孩子活着
When you left this morng, there were four.
你今早离开的时候 有四个
When you came home, there were still four.
你回来的时候 还会是四个
When you come home and there are only three,
当你回来却只有三个的时候
then you get to lecture me.
那你才能教训我
Excuse me.
打搅一下
Are you bree van de kamp?
- 您是 Bree Van de Camp吗?
Uh,yes,i am.
呃 是的 我是
My name is leila mitzman. I hope i'm not interrupting.
我叫 Leila Mitzman 我希望没打搅到您
Can i help you?
我能帮您什么?
This may sound odd, but i felt i should see you.
这也许听起来很怪 但我觉得我应该见您
I read in the paper that you're engaged to george williams.
我在报纸上看到 您和George Williams订婚的消息了
Oh,well,that announcement was a bit premature.
哦 那个公告有点太早了
But you and george are involved...
但您和George...
in a romantic relationship?
确实相爱?
Yes.
是的
Then we need to talk.
那我们需要谈谈
when he asked me to marry him.
我们约会了6个月后 他说要我嫁给他
From the moment i said "yes," george got so possessive,
从我说“我愿意”那一刻起 George 就变得占有欲极强
and when he found out
当他发现我前夫就住在同一条街上
my ex lived just down the street,
george accused me of seeing him behind his back.
George就说我背着他和他见面
And then one night, i got a call from the police.
然后一天晚上 我接到警察的电话
Someone had set my ex's car on fire.
有人烧了我前夫的车
I could never prove anything,
我什么都不能证明
but i knew it was george. I left him the next day.
但我知道是George干的 我第二天就离开了他
Well,i don't know what to say.
哦 我真不知道说什么好
I know. It's upsetting.
我知道 这真令人不安
Yes,it is...
确实...
to have a complete stranger come into my home,
让一个完全陌生的人来我家
drink my tea,
喝我的茶
one of the sweetest men i have ever known.
然后试图让我对这辈子见过最好的男人翻脸
Honey,you got to trust me. George is a whack job,
你得相信我 George不太正常
and you should get while the getting's good.
现在反悔还来得及
I think it's time for you to leave.
我想你该离开了
One time,i was talking to a guy at a bar,
有一次, 我在酒吧里跟一个家伙说话
and when we got home, george slapped me.
后来回家的时候, George扇了我个耳光
What do you say to that?
你怎么看?
and your freewheeling use of epithets,
我看 你这么失礼又乱称呼别人诨名
i'm willing to bet that he was provoked.
我肯定是你挑衅他的
When i read that you were engaged to george,
当我知道你和George订婚的时候
i felt it was my duty to let you know he's crazy.
我就觉得一定要告诉你他是个疯子
But now that i've met you,
但是现在我遇见了你
i can see it's a match made in heaven.
我觉得你们是天造地设的一对
I'm here. Hi,morty, reverend hopkins.
我在这 嗨 Morty hopkins牧师
I'm sorry i'm late to your rehearsal.
抱歉,你们的排练我来晚了
Oh,it's okay. It's all right. You're here now.
哦, 没有关系, 你现在来了就好
It's fine. Go in front of me.
好的, 到我前面来
Okay,reverend,hit it! (wagner's "wedding march" playing)
OK, 牧师, 放音乐
You've got to march,susie. Got to march. Oh.
你得走了, Susie 走吧
Oh. I was just researching my book,
哦, 我刚才在研究我的书
ani found the strangest thing.
发现了最奇怪的事
No one with my father's name was ever a merchant marine.
商船船员里没有一个人是叫爸爸的名字的
Oh,did i say merchant?
哦, 我说商船了?
Well,i just meant the regular marines.
我的意思就是一般的船
Oh,well,yeah,i thought you probably did.
哦 是的, 我也猜到你可能说错了
So i checked that,too, and he wasn't there,
所以我也查了, 但也没有他的名字
and so i called the v.a.,
所以我打电话去退伍军人事务部
and there is not a single record
根本没有一个叫Harrison Ross的人参加过越战
This is not the time,susie.
现在不是时候谈这个, Susie
What's... what's the holdup, ladies?
女士们, 怎么还慢慢吞吞的?
Well,i'm sorry to upset you,mom,i just...
我很抱歉让你难过, 妈妈, 只是...
don't you think that's weird?
你不认为这很奇怪?
What's... what's weird?
有...有什么奇怪的?
of anyone with my dad's name in the armed services.
服役记录中没有任何人叫爸爸那个名字的
Oh,well,there it is.
恩, 终于来了
There what is?
来什么了
Morty,just go on back up there.
Morty, 你站回去
Look,i'm... i'm not gonna say that
听着, 我不想说的 但我知道会有这一天
i knew this would happen, but i knew this would happen.
我早就料到会有这么一天
Mom,ieed answers.
妈妈, 我想知道答案
Do you have to do thisow?
必须现在吗?
You are ruining my wedding rehearsal.
你在给我的婚礼排练捣乱
Well,you've been married four times.
你都已经结过四次婚了 也没什么大不了的吧
I will nottand here and be attacked!
我不想浪费时间在这里听你损我!
Mom, don't walk away from me. Ow!
妈妈, 你别撇下我
What do you want me to say?
你要我说什么?
You want me to say i'm a bad mother?
你要我承认自己是个坏妈妈?
Fine! I'm a bad mother! Are you happy now?
好! 我是个坏妈妈! 你满意了?
Mom! Mom.
妈妈! 妈妈
(sophie crying) Mom.
妈妈
Yes,yes,l-i know what i'm getting into.
是的 我知道我在干什么
Morty? Morty, have you seen my mom?
Morty? Morty, 你看到我妈妈了吗?
Yeah. Yeah, she seemed,uh,
是的, 她看上去好像...
she seemed pretty upset. L-i think...
好像相当沮丧, 我想...
i think she took a cab home.
我想她已经打车回去了
You need... you need a ride?
需要...需要送你一程吗?
I need to you tell me the truth about my father.
我要你告诉我爸爸的真相
Hop in.
上车
When,uh, when i was in korea,
我, 厄, 当我在韩国的时候
i was stationed outside of,uh,pusan,
我被分配到釜山城外驻扎
we'd... we'd get these... these passes,you know,
然后我们...我们得到了...通行许可, 你知道...
and we'd... and we'd go into town,
然后...然后我们就进了城
and,you know,we'd have a... have a few beers,
然后, 我们就...就喝了几杯啤酒
and we used to call it r and r
当兵的时候我们习惯把这个叫做r 'n' r
in... in military lingo.
是的, 我想我知道什么是 r 'n' r （r'n'r指休闲娱乐放松）
Yeah,well,i know what r and r means.
So what does this have to do with my father?
这跟我的父亲有什么关系?
Well,that's... that's what i'm getting to.
厄, 这就是我要说的...
Um,a-anyway,there were these... these young ladies.
恩, 反正, 就是有一些...年轻女人
Professional...
专业的...
ladies if... if you know what i mean.
女人...如果你知道我的意思
O-okay. Long story short, l... it's just i never figured
好...好吧, 长话短说 我...我从来没想到
that my first time with a woman would... would be in an alley...
我的第一次...会是在一家韩国面馆后面的小巷里
behind a korean noodle stand with... with my fatigues
军裤一直脱到了脚踝处
Okay,again,w-what does this have to do with my father?
好吧, 好吧, 那这到底跟我父亲有什么关系?
We... we've all done things that,uh,you know,
我们...我们都干过, 你知道...
thate're ashamed of.
很丢脸的事 我是说, 你知道, 我们都...
I mean,you know,we all...
我是说, 你知道, 我们都...
we all have secrets.
我们都有秘密
Your... your... your father wasn't a war hero.
你的...你的...爸爸不是什么战斗英雄
And he... he wasn't in viet... vietnam.
他...他也没去过越南
Well,why would my mother tell me that?
那, 为什么我妈妈说他去过?
Uh,sophie wasn't... wasn't married to your father.
啊, Sophie根本...根本没嫁给你爸爸
I'm... i'm not... i'm not sure
我也...不清楚...她是否知道你爸爸叫什么
she even... she even knew his name.
Are you saying that i'm the result
你是说我是我妈一夜情之后生下来的?
of my mother having a one-night stand?
Well,like l... like i said, we've all,y know,
恩, 就像...就像我说的, 我们都...
we've... we've all done things
我们都...都做过丢脸的事...
George.
George
Bree. This is a surprise.
Bree 真没想到
I'm sorry to drop by unannounced,
对不起我没说一声就过来了
but i just had this disturbing visit
但刚刚你的一个老朋友才来找过我
from an old friend of yours, a leila mitzman.
Leila Mitzman
She,uh,shouldn't have contacted you.
她, 厄, 不应该去找你
Well,she did,and she said
但她找了我, 对我说了一些关于你的坏话
You should know that she's a renowned liar.
你该知道她说谎话出了名的
That's what i thought at first,
开始我也是这样想的
but then having had time to think about it,
但事后再想
i can't understand why she'd go to so much trouble.
我不理解她为什么要费神说这个
I mean,what would her motive be?
她的动机是什么?
She's obsessed with me. She still wants me.
她对我不死心 她还想得到我
Wasn't it obvious?
不够明显吗?
No.
不
The woman is absolutely certifiable.
这个女人绝对是疯了
What's more, i can prove it.
我还可以证明
Leila was a customer here.
Leila是这里的顾客
Even though she's no longer welcome,
尽管她已经不受欢迎
we still keep her prescriptions on file.
我们仍把她的处方保留在案
"Fluoxetine,100 milligrams."
"Fluoxetine,100毫克"
"Risperidone,250 mil"... i'm sorry. What is this?
"Risperidone,250毫克"... 对不起 这是什么?
One is an antidepressant for mood swings.
一个是治疗情绪波动的抗抑郁药
One is an antipsychotic
还有个是治疗幻觉的安定药
to control hallucinations.
Like i said, she's a very troubled lady.
就像我说的 她是个有问题的女人
Well,then why did you date her in the first place?
那你一开始为什么和她交往?
In the beginning,you're blind to the flaws,right?
开始时你会对缺点视而不见,对吧?
That's true... in the beginning.
是的... 开始时
So we're good?
那么我们之间没问题了吧?
(sighs) yeah, of course we are.
是的,没有了
Your mail came.
有你的信
You said you were leaving.
你说你走的
No,i said i was giving you space.
不,我说我要给你空间
I did. I was watchin' you from my car.
我做到了,我从车里看着你
Look,the guy who broke in stole ice cream.
听着 那人闯进来为了偷冰淇淋
I don't think i'm in any danger.
我不认为我有什么危险
So you can go. I don't need you.
所以你可以走了 我不需要你
Carlos says you do.
Carlos说需要
Where are you going?
去哪?
Shopping... not that it's any of your business.
购物，和你没关系
You sure like to shop.
- 你喜欢购物啊
Yes,i do.
是的
That's all i've seen you do the past day and a half.
这一天半我看到你都在购物
Uh-huh.
是啊
All that shopping must be making up for something.
购物可以补偿什么了吧
Excuse me?
什么?
You know, carlos has your number.
carlos有你的号码
He says you're one tough cookie.
他说你意志坚强
So tough,you don't have to deal with your feelings.
坚强到你都不用处理你的感情
He's a perceptive man.
他会看人 他以为我和两个同性恋有染
He thought i was cheating with two gay guys.
他以为我和两个同性恋有染
Are you sure you want to go with perceptive? Well,let's see.
你确信他会看人?
It's been what,a week since you lost your baby?
你失去孩子后有一个星期了吧?
Yeah,so?
是又怎么样?
So i never heard of shopping out the pain.
我从没听过可以用购物来抚平心灵创伤
Why is everye on my back about this?
为什么每个人在我背后都说这些?
I will deal with my loss my way,okay?!
我自然有我的方法! 知道了?
Where are you going?
你去哪啊?
Ah,i,uh,i just thought
我想我应该出去再看看
i'm gonna try the park.
- 我去公园找
In the middle of the night?
半夜去?
Well,yeah. Well,he hasn't really been showing his face
是啊,白天他不会出现的，不是吗?
in the daylight,has he?
Or would you rather we just let caleb run loose?
难道你宁愿让他逃亡?
He could be in trouble...
他会惹上麻烦
or hurting another girl.
或伤害另一个女人
He didn't hurt mrs. Solismatthew.
他没有伤害Solis太太 Matthew
He was just hungry.
他只是饿了
Yeah,well,i wasn't talking about mrs. Solis,
对，我没在说Solis太太
but you know that.
但你是了解的
So are you still going to be my matron of honor?
你还会做我的伴娘吗?
Of course i am.
当然会
i'm not still a little freaked out. I am.
我不会装作我没有抓狂 我还是的
But i did a lot of thinking about it this morning,
但早上我想了很久
and l-i think i understand.
我想我了解
You wanted to protect me,
你要保护我
and you thought i needed a hero.
你认为我需要个英雄
I had one. You.
我有,就是你
I was always so worried i would screw you up.
我一直担心我会毁了你
Well,i am screwed up, but it wasn't your fault...
我现在是毁了,但不是你的原因
entirely. Oh.
根本不是
Hey,stu.
嘿,stu
You busy?
你忙吗?
No,just updating my blog.
不,在更新我的博客
'Cause i've got an important assignment for you.
因为我有个重要的任务给你
to take on more responsibility around here.
太好了 我准备好承担更多的责任了
Yeah,i applaud that, but what i need
对,我很欣赏 但我要你做的是
is for you to help me to prove a point...
帮我证明一个观点
to my husband.
给我老公看
Oh. You want to make him jealous.
噢，你想让他吃醋 不是
Uh,no. (chuckles)
不是 实际上...
Actually...
实际上...
i need you to kidnap my children.
我要你绑架我的孩子
Okay,so what am i supposed to be lookin' at?
那么,我要看什么啊?
Just wait for it.
等一下
Okay,he he comes.
好的，他来了
What's goin' on?
会发生什么?
I'm just trying to prove a point.
我要证明一点
Hi...
嗨
little boys.
小伙子们
Hell,who is that?
那人是谁?
It's... it's just stu from our office.
是我们公司的Stu
You guys want to go for a ride?
你们要上车吗?
And is he abducting our kids?
他在绑架我们的孩子?
Maybe.
也许 疯狂
(tom) this is crazy.
疯狂
Why? Are you worried they might get in?
为什么，你担心他们进车?
We can go to the,uh,carnival.
我们去...嘉年华
You like carnivals?
喜欢嘉年华?
We're not allowed to talk to strangers.
我们不准和陌生人说话
Run,boys.
快跑啊 孩子们
So,uh,
那么 你们为什么不进车
why don't you boys get in the car...
你们为什么不进车
run away. Run.
跑开,跑啊
Get in the car, and i'll give you some candy.
进来,我就给你们吃糖 好,有糖吃咯
Why aren't they running away?
他们为什么不跑?
Well...
恩... 现在不是得意的时候
this is not the time to be smug.
现在不是得意的时候
Clearly our sons are...
很明显我们的孩子是
idiots.
很明显我们的孩子是 笨蛋
Okay,okay,jeez.
给,给
Hi.
嗨
(gasps) oh,my god! (stu) ow!
我的天哪
Run,kids,run! Run! No,you don't.
孩子们,快跑 你别想
You pervert! Oh,no, you're not goin' anywhere!
你这个变态,你哪都去不了啦
Um,a-anyway,after... after we... we wrap this shindig,
总之，婚礼结束后
i'm whisking my new bride, uh,away
我要把新娘带走
on a 4-month cruise around the world.
进行4个月的环球旅行
L-i would have been happy with a-a weekend in vegas,
我本想到拉斯维加斯去一个星期的
Anyway,here... here she is.
这个就是我的妻子
My,um,my beautiful bride.
我漂亮的妻子
I want to thank everyone for coming,
感谢大家的到来
who's helped me
他帮我成为了个更好的人
be a bter person.
And i want to thank...
我要感谢
my amazing daughter susan, and tell her
我出色的女儿Susan
how much i appreciate her love and respect...
要告诉她我是如何感激 她对我的爱和尊敬
because i'm a horrible person,
因为我是个糟糕的人
and she deserves so much better than me.
她应该比我得到更好的
Honey,honey.
- 亲爱的，亲爱的
No,nono,no,no.
不，不
Susan needs to know the truth.
Susan该知道真相
Your father...
你父亲
was not a one-night stand.
不是搞一夜情的人
He was 33, and he was married...
他33岁了,已婚
and he was my boss.
而且他是我的上司
When i told him i was pregnant,
当我对他说我怀孕时
he broke it off,and he never spoke to me again.
就和我分手，再也不和我说话了
But he gave me my beautiful, incredible daughter,
但留给了我一个漂亮的好女儿
and for that, i want to thank addison prudy.
为了这个原因 我要感谢Addsion Prudy
Oh,my god.
天啊
Do you know where he is?
你知道他在哪吗?
I have no idea. I swear, if i knew,l-i wouldell you.
我不知道，我发誓，我知道会告诉你的
Uh,i know addison prudy.
我知道Addison Prudy
He runs the feed and supply store at third and sutherland.
他在third and sutherland 经营个日常用品商店
Uh,prudy's a fairly common name of... so.
Prudy是个很普遍的名字,所以...
Is that him?
是他吗?
Yes.
是的
Are you saying that all this time
你是说我的父亲一直活着
right across town running thsupply and feed store?
就在城外经营动物饲料店?
You're not... you're not still... still seeing him,are you?
你现在没和他约会吧？
Is something wrong?
怎么了?
You've been so quiet all evening.
你整晚都不怎么说话
No,no,i'm just tired, that's all.
不，我只是有点累
Care to dance? It might pep you up.
想跳舞吗?会让你精神一点
I don't think so. But thank you,though.
我不想跳，谢谢
Bree,where is your ring?
Bree,你的戒指呢?
Oh,um,the... the stone is loose.
哦，恩...钻石松了 所以我得送到珠宝店去
But don't worry, it's safe.
别担心，没事的
This isn't about leila, is it?
和leila没关系，是吗
No. No. It's like i told you,
是的，是的，正如我告诉你的
the stone could just pop off at anyecond.
只是担心钻石可能不小心掉下来
Well,i don't care. Please put it on.
恩，我不管，你还是戴上吧
What?
什么?
I want you to wear it.
我想让你戴上它
Well,i'm sorry, but i'm not going to.
恩，对不起，我不戴
Why not?
为什么?
Because i don't feel like it.
因为我不喜欢这样
And this is the last time we're gonna talk about this,okay?
以后别谈这个了，好吗?
Excuse me,ma'am.
对不起，夫人
We don't allow members of zeta beta kappa in here.
这不允许成绩得Z，B和P的人进入
Ty! Ty grant.
Ty! Ty grant
Oh,hi! What are you doing in town?
哦,嗨!你在城里干什么?
Visiting my folks.
走亲戚
Oh,my goodness. Oh,george,this is ty grant.
哦，见到你真好， 哦，george,这是ty grant
We used to date in college.
我们以前在大学约会过
Ty,this is george,um...
Ty,这是george,恩...
he's a good friend of mine.
他是我的好朋友
Actually,we're engaged.
事实上，我们定婚了
Bree,you look fantastic. You haven't aged a day.
Bree,你看起来真漂亮，一点也不显老 Ty,你想跳舞吗?
Ty,would you like to dance?
Ty,你想跳舞吗?
Sure. I'd love to.
当然，很高兴与你共舞
Let me take your coat.
我帮你脱衣服
need to cut in.
打断一下
George,would you please sit down?
George,你坐下好吗?
You're being rude.
你太粗鲁了
Am i in the middle of something?
我妨碍什么事了吗? 好吧，至少应该戴上戒指吧
No. George,i don't want to.
不，George,我不想戴
We are engaged. You have to wear it!
我们定婚了，你必须戴!
Hey,knock it off,man. George,stop it.
嗨,放开她， George,别这样
I'm sorry.
对不起
I just...
我只是...
we're engaged.
我们定婚了
See,the thing is, i don't think we are anymore.
你都看到了?我想我们没关系了
Please... you should go.
请你走开
Right over there,sir.
在那边,先生
Management likes us to keep the nice cars out front.
管理员总是把好车放在前面
Afternoon.
下午好
New hairdo?
- 换了新发型?
So what if it is?
是又怎么样?
It looks nice,that's all.
看上去不错,没别的
You know, i also got a facial,
我还做了美容
and later on i'm gonna get a pedicure
过会我还要做足疗,还要纹眉
It'sine with me.
这和我没关系
No,it's not,because i know what you're thinking.
不,有关系,因为我知道你在想什么
Yeah? You know what?
是吗? 你知道什么?
I am tired of you judging me.
我讨厌你指挥我
What is it gonna take to get rid of you,hmm?
怎么做才能甩掉你,恩?
What's your last name?
你姓什么? Ramos
Ramos. Here is $1,000.
Ramos,这儿有一千块
I won't tell carlos you didn't stick around.
我不会告诉carlos
It'll be our little secret.
这是我们之间的小秘密
I just got out of prison.
我刚从监狱出来
I'm not exactly set up with a bank account.
还没银行帐户
Can we go to your bank and cash this?
我们去银行换成现金如何?
And then you'll leave?
然后你就离开?
Hey,it's a grand.
嗨,这可是一千块啊
Buckle up.
系上安全带
You don't have a-a window thingy.
你没摇窗的?
Nope.
没有
You don't have a door handle either.
连门把手也没有?
Nope.
没有
But i do have a confession to make.
但我确实有些事要说
Carlos didn't really send me to protect you.
Carlos并没有派我保护你
Go figure.
你瞧
No one else in the park.
公园里没有人
We got it all to ourselves.
这儿都是我们的啦
Perfect.
真好
Why don't you go find us a good spot?
你为什么不去找个好地方?
I gotta get something out of the trunk.
我得从后备箱里拿点东西
Hey,where the hell you goin'?
嗨,你去哪?
You're not gonna kill me?
你不是准备要杀我?
I hadn't planned on it.
我没这计划
Besides,if i was gonna kill you,
而且,如果我想杀你 也不会用气球吧
i wouldn't use a balloon.
也不会用气球吧
It would take too long.
那太费劲了
What am i supposed to think? You lie about protecting me
你让我怎么想?你撒谎说保护我
and then you lock me in that heap without door handles
把我锁在那辆连门把手都没有的车里 我出都出不来
so i can't get out.
我出都出不来
Carlos sent me to help you with your grief.
Carlos派我帮你忘却悲伤
You're kidding,right?
你在开玩笑,对吗?
No.
不是
Look,i know a little somethin' about loss.
我知道失去亲人的感觉
It can take you to some real dark places,
让人变得非常阴暗
especially if you don't face it head-on,
尤其如果你不能一开始就正视问题
like 17 years in a 6x10 prison cell.
比如17年都在窄小的监狱房间里
Dark.
确实黑暗
What's this for?
这是干什么的？
The balloon represents the spirit of the life lost.
气球代表了失去的灵魂
By lettin' it go,
让他们飘走
you're acknowledging the pain you feel
你就正视了自己的痛苦
and releasin' it at the same time.
并且释放出来
Okay,that's ridiculous.
这太荒唐了
Besides,i don't feel what you think i'm feeling.
而且你并不知道我的感觉
Then it should be real easy.
那这就很简单了
Okay... should i say something?
咱们来说点什么？
If you want to.
如果你想…
Not really,no.
不大想
It's cool.
没关系
Anytime.
只要你想，随时都可以
This is stupid.
这太糟糕了
I didn't even want this baby.
我甚至不想生小孩
Yeah.
对
And i would've been a terrible mother.
我不可能是个好母亲
If you say so.
你说什么就是什么
If it was a boy, i was gonna name it charlie.
如果是个男孩，我想起名Charlie
Yeah?
哦？
And a girl,aurora.
女孩就叫Aurora
Those are nice names.
很好听的名字
Yeah.
谢谢
Thank you.
What is it,boy?
怎么了，孩子？
What's goin' on out here?
发生什么事情了？
Call the police. You need me to zap him?
报警 我去揍他吧？
Just call the police.
报警就是了
Is that the guy who broke into your house?
是那个闯进你家的人？
Uh,i don't know. I can't see him.
不知道 我看不见他
Yeah,that's him.
对，就是他
In a world filled with darkness,
[在一个黑暗的世界里]
we all need some kind of light.
[我们都需要一点光明]
Whether it's a great flame that shows us
[也许是一束光明]
how to win back what we've lost,
[让我们知道怎么挽回失去的东西]
or a powerful beacon
[或是一个灯塔]
intended to scare away potential monsters...
[驱走生命中的恶魔] [2，4，6，8]
or a few glowing bulbs that reveal to us
[或者是几个灯泡]
the hidden truth ofur past...
[照亮了掩盖住的真相]
to help us get through the night...
[黑暗中我们都需要一些光明]
even if it's just the tiniest glimmer of hope.
[哪怕只是最微弱的希望]
-=筱闲工作室=- 时间轴：Hill
-=伊甸园论坛 http://www.ydy.com=- 荣誉出品 绝望主妇 第二季第八集